Guide to the Lorenzo and Ruth Bennett Morgan Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Family Correspondence, 1862-2001; Series I
  - LSM/RBM to/from their children
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, 1936 Apr - Jun (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, 1936 Jul - Sep (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, incl. RPM's husband Hubert Schmidt; CBM at Univ. of Illinois, 1936 Oct - Dec (Box 11, Folder 182)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, incl. RPM's husband Hubert Schmidt; CBM at Univ. of Illinois, 1937 Jan - Mar (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, incl. RPM's husband Hubert Schmidt; CBM at Univ. of Illinois, 1937 Apr - Jun (Box 11, Folder 184)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, incl. RPM's husband Hubert Schmidt, 1937 Jul - Aug (Box 11, Folder 185)
    - Incl. re. Japanese invasion of China, 1937 Sep - Dec (Box 11, Folder 186-187)
    - Incl. re. Japanese invasion of China; birth of grandchild, 1938 Jan - Mar (Box 12, Folder 188)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, 1938 Apr - Jun (Box 12, Folder 189)
    - Primarily to/from CBM, 1938 Jul - 1939 Jun (Box 12, Folder 190-192)
    - Incl. map of Wuhu General Hospital, and re. bandit robberies, 1939 Jul - Dec (Box 12, Folder 193)
    - To/from RPM, JLM, CBM, 1940-1941 Jun (Box 12, Folder 194-195)
    - Primarily to/from CBM, wife Dorothy (DDM), 1941 Jul - Dec (Box 12, Folder 196)
    - Primarily to/from CBM/DDM, 1942 (Box 12, Folder 197)
    - Incl. from LSM during internment in Wuhu, 1943 Jan - Dec (Box 12, Folder 198-199)
    - To/from RBM and children, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - Incl. from LSM in internment in Shanghai, Internaion; V-Mail to CBM during war, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - Primarily to/from CBM/DDM, 1946 - 1955 (Box 12, Folder 202-203)
  - Morgan children to extended family / friends
    - Letters, 1916 - 1949 (Box 13, Folder 204-216)
    - Letters re. parents' deaths / Letters of condolence, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 217)
    - Carrel Morgan to/from friends, 1963 - 2001 (Box 13, Folder 218)
  - Correspondence of LSM family
    - Letters to/from Blanche Morgan and Mary Bennett, nieces, nephews, friends, 1904 - 1919 (Box 13, Folder 219)
    - Letters of children of grandmother Morgan, Blanche Morgan, nieces, 1920 - 1928 (Box 13, Folder 220)
    - Letters of children of grandmother Morgan, Blanche Morgan, nieces, 1929 - 1955 (Box 14, Folder 221)
  - Correspondence of RBM family
    - Letter to RBM's father, 1862 (Box 14, Folder 222)
    - Letters to/from Mary Bennett and son Ralph, 1899 (Box 14, Folder 222)
    - Mary Bennett to/from son Ralph, 1900-1903 (Box 14, Folder 223-226)
    - Letters of Mary Bennett, Ralph, and Mary's sister Belle, 1904 - 1910 (Box 14, Folder 227)
    - Letters of Mary Bennett and Ralph Bennett, 1911 - 1946 (Box 14, Folder 228)
    - Fragments, letters of Mary Bennett and Ralph Bennett (Box 14, Folder 229)
- General Correspondence, 1900-1990; Series II
  - Morgan circular letters, 1913, 1930, 1940, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 230)
  - A (Recipients /senders with names beginning with A) (Box 14, Folder 231)
  - B (Box 14, Folder 232, 233)
  - C (Box 15, Folder 234 - 236)
  - Cardiff, Ira, 1914 - 1955 (Box 15, Folder 237)
  - Cartwright, Frank T., 1945 - 1949 (Box 15, Folder 238)
  - Craighill, Lloyd, 1943 - 1950 (Box 15, Folder 239)
  - Culley, Frances, 1939 - 1955 (Box 15, Folder 240)
  - Currie, Ed and Gay, 1930 - 1953 (Box 15, Folder 241)
  - D (Box 15, Folder 242)
  - Djang, Helen, 1923 - 1955 (Box 15, Folder 243)
  - E (Box 15, Folder 244)
  - F (Box 15, Folder 245)
  - G (Box 15, Folder 246)
  - Gale, Frank and Ailie, 1930 - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 247)
  - Grafton, Thomas, Letty and Mary, 1910 - 1926 (Box 16, Folder 248)
  - Grafton, Thomas, Letty and Mary, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 249)
  - Grafton, Thomas, Letty and Mary, 1928 - 1929 (Box 16, Folder 250)
  - Grafton, Thomas, Letty and Mary, 1930 - 1933 (Box 16, Folder 251)
  - Grafton, Thomas, Letty and Mary, 1934 - 1950 (Box 16, Folder 252)
  - Grafton circulars / Cornelius Grafton, 1926 -1946 (Box 16, Folder 253)
  - H (Box 16, Folder 254)
  - Hayes, Sister Constance Ann, 1939 - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 255)
  - Hsue, Berta Muller, 1939 - 1945 (Box 16, Folder 256)
  - Hwang, Edith, 1948 - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 257)
  - I, 1905 - 1945 (Box 17, Folder 258)
  - Imperial Japanese Consulate, 1942 - 1943 (Box 17, Folder 259)
  - J (Box 17, Folder 260)
  - K (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - L (Box 17, Folder 262 - 263)
  - Lanphear, B. W., 1945 -1951 (Box 17, Folder 264)
  - Liu, Frances, 1939 - 1953 (Box 17, Folder 265)
  - Mc / Mac (Box 17, Folder 266)
  - MacGregor, Flora, 1948 - 1955 (Box 17, Folder 267)
  - McLauchlin, W. C. and Elizabeth, 1927 - 1953 (Box 17, Folder 268)
  - M (Box 17, Folder 269 - 270)
  - Mission Board: Presbyterian Church in the U.S., 1904 - 1919 (Box 17, Folder 271)
  - Mission Board: Presbyterian Church in the U.S., 1920 - 1941 (Box 17, Folder 272)
  - Mission Board: Methodist Church, 1941 - 1946 (Box 17, Folder 273)
  - N (Box 17, Folder 274)
  - Nee, Gilbert, 1946 -1948 (Box 17, Folder 275)
  - O (Box 18, Folder 276)
  - P (Box 18, Folder 277)
  - Paxton, John and Una Hall Paxton, 1905 - 1920 (Box 18, Folder 278)
  - Paxton, J. Hall and Vincoe, 1950 - 1957 (Box 18, Folder 279)
  - R (Box 18, Folder 280)
  - Rice, A. D. and Emma, 1919 - 1933 (Box 18, Folder 281)
  - de Roo de la Faille, L., 1923 - 1947 (Box 18, Folder 282)
  - S (Box 18, Folder 283 - 285)
  - Shih, Irene Chu, 1934 - 1950 (Box 18, Folder 286)
  - Stillians, Arthur and Effie, 1895 - 1948 (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - Swiss Consulate General, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 288)
  - T (Box 18, Folder 289)
  - U (Box 18, Folder 290)
  - Urquhart / Vinson, 1945, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 291)
  - V (Box 18, Folder 292)
  - Vinson family (see also Collected Material), 1926 - 1953 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - W (Box 19, Folder 294 - 296)
  - Watters, Hyla, 1937 -1955 (Box 19, Folder 297)
  - Wenner, Frank and Lottie, 1912 - 1954 (Box 19, Folder 298)
  - Whiteley, Annie, 1912 -1933 (Box 19, Folder 299)
  - Woodbridge, Casper, 1908 - 1927 (Box 19, Folder 300)
  - Woods, James, 1904 - 1951 (Box 19, Folder 301)
  - Y (Box 19, Folder 302)
  - Correspondence of others: C - L: incl. Cassidy, Grafton, Hayes (Box 19, Folder 303)
  - Correspondence of others: M - Y: incl. McLauchlin, Nee, Woods, Youtsey (Box 19, Folder 304)
  - Chinese language letters (Box 19, Folder 305)
- Writings, 1895-2001; Series III
  - Articles, Reports, Notes
    - By LSM
      - High school and pre-high school era (Box 20, Folder 306)
      - College essays, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 307)
      - College essays, 1897 Jan - Mar (Box 20, Folder 308)
      - College essays, incl. Junior Oration, 1897 Oct, 1898 (Box 20, Folder 309)
      - College essays, incl. Senior Essay, 1899 (Box 20, Folder 310)
      - College essays, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 311)
      - College notebooks, 1897 (Box 20, Folder 312)
      - While stationed at Tsingkiang Pu; incl. re. bandits, famine, anti-opium crusade, Chinese government practices, 1906 - 1910 (Box 20, Folder 313)
      - While stationed at Haichow; incl. re. famine relief, medical work, opium, Christmas celebration, 1911 - 1912 (Box 20, Folder 314, 315)
      - While stationed at Haichow; incl. re. robbers, Ellen Lavine Graham Hospital, 1913 - 1914 (Box 20, Folder 316)
      - While stationed at Haichow; incl. personal report of work, re. military situation, medical work, looting and burning of Haichow, fighting pneumonic plague in Tatung (seealso compiled packets of documentation in Collected Materials, Box 33), 1915 - 1919 (Box 20, Folder 317)
      - While stationed at Haichow; incl. re. hospital work, banditry, battle at Chinkiang, Lunghai Railway, 1923 - 1925 (Box 20, Folder 318)
      - While stationed at Haichow; incl. re. bandit situation, floods, political situation, medical missionary work, 1926 - 1929 (Box 21, Folder 319)
      - While stationed at Haichow and Wuhu; incl. re. bandit situation, treatment of Kala Azar, bicycling from Chinkiang to Nanking, Wuhu General Hospital, 1930 - 1936 (Box 21, Folder 320)
      - While stationed at Wuhu; incl. re. Japanese occupation, Wuhu General Hospital, 1938 - 1939 (Box 21, Folder 321)
      - While stationed at Wuhu, incl. re. Wuhu General Hospital, 1940 - 1946 (Box 21, Folder 322)
      - Notes for various talks, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 323)
    - By other family members
      - By RBM, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 324)
      - By Ruth Pearce Morgan, incl. poems in published booklet "Bamboos - reaching up" (includes poems from other Shanghai American School students), 1912 - 1929 (Box 21, Folder 325)
      - By Ruth Pearce Morgan, 1930 - 1939 (Box 21, Folder 326)
      - By Carrel Morgan, 1928 - 2001 (Box 21, Folder 327)
    - Writings of others
      - Betts, Brown, Corpron, Djan, Dunn, Gaud, 1904 - 1949 (Box 21, Folder 328)
      - Hallett, James, Stillians, Watters, 1937 - 1939 (Box 21, Folder 329)
  - Diaries
    - Diaries of LSM
      - Original diaries - three small notebooks, 1901, 1944 Mar - 1945 May 12 at ASH Camp, 1945 May 13 - 1946 Mar 30 at ASH Camp, 1901 -1946 (Box 21, Folder 330-331)
      - Photocopies of LSM diary while interned at Argyle Southern Highlanders (ASH) Camp at the Civil Assembly Center, Shanghai., 1944 Mar - 1945 May 12 (Box 21, Folder 332)
      - Photocopies of LSM diary while interned, 1945 May 13 - 1946 Mar (Box 22, Folder 333)
      - Photocopies of LSM diary, 1948 Nov 22 - 1949 Jan 26 (Box 22, Folder 334)
      - Typed transcript of LSM diary while interned at ASH camp, 1944 Mar - 1946 Mar (Box 22, Folder 335)
      - LSM diary, letters, photos, documents war time experience and internment, compiled with index and commentary by Carrel Morgan (3 editions), 1941 - 1946 (Box 22, Folder 336)
    - Diaries of other family members
      - Of RBM and Ruth Pearce Morgan, 1921 - 1923, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 337)
      - Of RBM, 1926 - 1936 (Box 22, Folder 338-340)
      - Of RBM, 1937 - 1938 (Box 23, Folder 341)
      - Of Ruth Pearce Morgan, 1926 - 1929 (Box 23, Folder 342)
  - Notebooks / compilations
    - LSM Address books and lists (Box 23, Folder 343)
    - LSM and RBM appointment books, notebooks (Box 23, Folder 344)
    - Guestbooks of RBM (Box 23, Folder 345 - 346)
    - Scrapbooks of RBM, 1930s (Box 23, Folder 347 -348)
- Biographical Information, 1868-1955; Series IV
  - Morgan and Bennett families
    - Genealogical information, misc. early legal and real estate documents, letters, and notices related to family members, 1868-1904 (Box 24, Folder 349)
  - LSM
    - High school - Galva, IL; Knox College, 1895 - 1900 (Box 24, Folder 350)
    - Knox College - Year book, notebooks, 1897-1900 (Box 24, Folder 351)
    - Johns Hopkins Medical School and Marriage, 1901 - 1904 (Box 24, Folder 352)
    - Application and acceptance to be missionary, 1904 (Box 24, Folder 353)
    - Early years at Haichow, 1905 - 1912 (Box 24, Folder 354)
    - Later years at Haichow, 1923 - 1928 (Box 24, Folder 355)
    - Last years in Haichow, early years in Wuhu, 1930 - 1937 (Box 24, Folder 356)
    - In Wuhu, 1938 -1941 (Box 24, Folder 357)
    - Sale of items and rent receipts related to Japanese invasion, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 358)
    - Accounts related to internment incl. ASH camp, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 359)
    - Birthday cards for LSM's 69th - at ASH camp, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 360)
    - Records for dental clinic at ASH camp, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 361)
    - Records from ASH camp: dental reports, food parcels received, typed summary re. camp, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 362)
    - Return to U.S.A.; letters re. healthcare, LSM last will, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 363)
    - Life in NY and NJ until his death, 1952 - 1955 (Box 25, Folder 364)
    - Personal English and Chinese new Testaments and devotional books; Bibles (Box 25, Folder 365)
    - Documentation re. siblings and Morgan estate, 1924 - 1954 (Box 25, Folder 366)
  - Ruth Bennett Morgan
    - Early years and University of Illinois, 1888 - 1897 (Box 26, Folder 367)
    - University of Illinois, 1897 - 1899 Feb (Box 26, Folder 368)
    - University of Illinois and calling card collection, 1899 (Box 26, Folder 369)
    - Medical school, Johns Hopkins University, 1900 - 1904 (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - Johns Hopkins University - financial records, 1900 - 1904 (Box 26, Folder 371)
    - Wedding invitation; certificate of missionary appointment; Chinese language study books, 1904 - 1908 (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - Record books; personal materials - Haichow era; passport; program from Thanksgiving missionary event, 1920 - 1932 (Box 26, Folder 373)
    - Miscellaneous forms; Health report; Wuhu hospital formulary, 1931 - 1939 (Box 26, Folder 374)
    - Pass for Japanese security; Chinese devotional book; Bible, 1941, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 375)
    - Municipal loan documents, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 376)
    - War ration book; obituaries; condolences, 1942 - 1955 (Box 26, Folder 377)
    - Misc. Chinese language flyers, invitations, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 377)
  - Morgan children
    - Ruth Pearce Morgan Schmidt, 1924- 1936 (Box 27, Folder 378)
    - Juliana "Jimmy" Morgan, 1930s (Box 27, Folder 379)
    - Carrel Morgan - early years, 1928 -1932 (Box 27, Folder 380)
    - Carrel Morgan - school reports, finances, 1927 - 1936 (Box 27, Folder 381)
    - Carrel Morgan - school health records, wedding picture, 1932 - 1934, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 382)
- Collected Material, 1900-1994; Series V
  - Artifacts / memorabilia
    - Christmas cards, postcards, misc. (Box 27, Folder 383)
    - Insignia from ASH camp, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Miscellaneous items incl. notes re. plaques received; diskette "China Remembers Medical Missions" (Box 27, Folder 385)
    - Parachute fabric; Chinese money, 1937 - 1939 (Box 27, Folder 386)
    - Black and white drawings; Chinese scrolls; Burned wooden figure; Chinese coins (Box OV-2)
    - Chinese garment for child; handsewn bag; large fabric (possibly a garment) (Box OV-3)
    - Cloth dolls representing a Chinese family, an evangelist, and nurses (Grandfather, grandmother, farmer, farmer's wife, son, daughter-in-law, daughter, servant, evangelist, 3 nurses), 1930s (Box OV-4)
      Scope and Contents
      The dolls were made by women at the True Light industrial mission. Ruth Morgan used the dolls when giving talks to churches and other organizations in the U.S.
    - Two cloth models of bedding rolls used by the Morgans, made by women at True Light mission, 1930s (Box OV-4)
    - Embroidered shoes for child with bound feet; embroidered cloth booties, 1930s-1940s (Box OV-4)
    - Embroidered cloth items, including baby's bonnet, bib, clothing, 1930s- 1940s (Box OV-5)
    - Packet of raw silk, wooden chopsticks, decorative pins in small box; cut-paper designs, stamped paper with blue design, piece of wood with intricate carved design, box of keepsakes of Ruth Morgan, three boxes of metal brooches, pins, and buttons, silk pendant necklace, 1930s-1940s, n.d. (Box OV-5)
    - Covered straw basket containing box of "ancient Chinese buttons", "ditty bag" given to Loren Morgan by American Red Cross at internment camp or on ship home, blue and white patterned cloth, 1930s-1940s, n.d. (Box OV-5)
    - Medal given to Dr. L. Morgan for his work in the plague epidemic, several small handbags of various designs, box containing blue-enameled beads "worn at some Imperial funeral by a Chinese official", carved stone items including two "chops", small case with "chop", compass in wooden case, 1930-1940s, n.d. (Box OV-6)
    - Two small framed paintings of Chinese people, carved wooden pieces, decorated paper fan,metal decorated box with two small dishes, metal box containing buttons, several metal items, 1930s-1940s, n.d. (Box OV-6)
    - Embroidered / appliqued table linens, n.d. (Box OV-7)
    - Poster with text and illustration of Bible story, wedding invitation, slips of red paper with Chinese characters on them, tract (Box OV-7)
  - Art work
    - Drawings and prints (Box 27, Folder 387)
    - Chinese portrayal of Prodigal Son (Box 27, Folder 388)
    - Sketches of mission compound; Chinese portrayal of Hell (Box 27, Folder 389)
    - Drawings by RBM while at University of Illinois (Box OV-2)
  - Publications
    - Books, booklets, brochures
      - Flyers, programs, tracts,sermons, 1911 - 1946 (Box 28, Folder 390)
      - Booklets, tracts, psychological tests for missionary candidates, 1900 - 1950 (Box 28, Folder 391)
      - Booklets, "Conquest by Healing in China", Report of special mission to China, 1946, 1927 - 1973 (Box 28, Folder 392)
      - Sunday School pictures of Chinese chldren (Box 28, Folder 393)
      - Various booklets and brochures, incl. re. sex, 1937 - 1950 (Box 28, Folder 394)
      - Misc. bulletins; report on "Lessons to be Learned from the Experiences of Christian Missions in China", 1941 - 1951 (Box 28, Folder 395)
      - Prayer cycle book; directories (JHU 1938), 1937 - 1945 (Box 28, Folder 396)
      - Tsingtao guide book; prayer book; "A New Digest of Japanese War Conduct", 1934 - 1941 (Box 28, Folder 397)
    - Newsletters and magazines re. China
      - Newsletters of Board of Foreign Missions, Methodist Church, 1939 Jan - 1942 Feb (Box 28, Folder 398)
      - Newsletters of Board of Foreign Missions, Methodist Church, 1942 Jun - 1946 Dec (Box 28, Folder 399)
      - China Bulletin - Division of Foreign Missions, National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., 1951 Nov - 1953 Aug (Box 29, Folder 400)
      - China Bulletin - Division of Foreign Missions, National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A., 1953 Sep - 1954 Nov (Box 29, Folder 401)
      - Publications of Board of Foreign Missions, Presbyterian Church, National Council Protestant Episcopal Church, etc., 1942 - 1947 (Box 29, Folder 402)
      - Bulletins re. China; "China Connection"; Shanghai American School newsletter, 1941 - 1998 (Box 29, Folder 403)
      - "China in Chaos", 1927 (Box 29, Folder 404)
      - "The China Monthly", 1944 Nov - 1945 May (Box 29, Folder 405)
      - "The China Weekly Review", 1925 - 1928 (Box 29, Folder 406)
      - "The China Weekly Review", 1940 (Box 29, Folder 407)
      - "Free Wan-Kam", 1942 Feb - 1944 Feb (Box 29, Folder 408)
      - "Prisoner of War Bulletin", 1944 Jul - 1945 Aug (Box 29, Folder 409)
      - United China Relief, 1941 - 1945 (Box 29, Folder 410)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings
      - Re. various missionaries, 1925 - 1927 (Box 30, Folder 412)
      - Clippings re. China - events, etc., 1905, 1925 - 1926 (Box 30, Folder 413)
      - Clippings re. China - events, etc., 1927 (Box 30, Folder 414)
      - Chinese newspaper clippings, 1927 Mar (Box 30, Folder 415)
      - American newspaper clippings, 1927 Mar - Apr (Box 30, Folder 416)
      - Chinese newspaper clippings, 1927 Apr - Jun (Box 30, Folder 417)
      - Misc. articles, 1929 - 1936 (Box 30, Folder 418)
      - Misc. articles, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 419-420)
      - Misc. articles, incl. re. Japanese invasion, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 421-422)
      - Misc. articles, incl. re. Japanese invasion, 1939 - 1940 (Box 31, Folder 423)
      - Misc. articles, incl. re. Japanese invasion, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 424)
      - Misc. articles re. World War II, 1942-1944 (Box 31, Folder 425-427)
      - Misc. articles - end of war, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 428)
      - American edition - Shanghai Evening Post, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 429-430a)
  - Maps
    - Various maps of China, 1900 - 1943 (Box 30, Folder 411)
    - Oversize maps of China (Box OV-1)
  - Topical subject files
    - American Consular Service
      - Documents and information, 1918, 1928, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 431-432)
    - Ellen Lavine Graham Hospital, Haichow
      - Plans, statistics, reports, 1913, 1928 (Box 32, Folder 433)
    - Wuhu General Hospital, Wuhu
      - Annual reports, 1932 - 1947 (Box 32, Folder 434)
      - Formulary, programs, calendars, 1939 - 1942 (Box 32, Folder 435)
    - German aviator in Tsingtao
      - Info. compiled b y CBM re. German aviator Plueschow, known as "The Dragon Master of Tsingtao, China" (Article in Sunset Magazine), 1914, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 436-437)
      - "The Dragon Master" - book by Robert A. Whitaker, published 1994 (Box 33, Folder 438)
    - Plague in Tatung (Packets compiled by CBM)
      - Packet I: News articles, 1918 Jan - Mar (Box 33, Folder 439)
      - Packets II and III: LSM letters, documents, 1918 Feb-Apr (Box 33, Folder 440-441)
    - John W. Vinson and family
      - Letters re. their life and Mrs. Vinson's death, 1910, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 442)
      - JWV's death at the hands of bandits - letters, documents, articles, audiotape, 1931 Nov, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 443)
    - Chinese students helped by LSM and RBM
      - Chen, Grace, 1949 - 1952 (Box 33, Folder 444)
      - Lee, James and Dora, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 445)
      - Lin, Michael F.C., 1953 - 1954 (Box 34, Folder 446)
      - Louie, Yam-Hin and Josephine, 1950 - 1954 (Box 34, Folder 447)
      - Tseng, Pauline (Mrs. Clayton Chu), 1951 - 1954 (Box 34, Folder 448)
      - Tsou, Szu-Tai (Stephen), 1949 - 1955 (Box 34, Folder 449)
      - Tung, Ai-Ling (Mrs. Szu-Tai Tsou), 1951 - 1955 (Box 34, Folder 450)
      - Wu, Louise, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 451)
      - Yu, Julia, 1950 - 1954 (Box 34, Folder 452)
- Photographs, 1885-2000; Series VI
  - People
    - Morgan family, 1885 - 1953 (Box 34, Folder 453-454)
    - Morgan family - scrapbook collection, 1910 - 1933 (Box 34, Folder 455)
    - Western colleagues and friends, 1900 - 1908 (Box 35, Folder 456)
    - Western colleagues and friend, 1912 - 1951 (Box 35, Folder 457)
    - Chinese people, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 460)
    - Chinese people - famine years, 1906 - 1907 (Box 35, Folder 461)
    - Chinese people, 1910 - 1953 (Box 35, Folder 462)
    - Chinese people, 1926 (Box OV-1)
  - Places
    - Ellen Lavine Graham Hospital, Haichow, 1904 - 1933 (Box 35, Folder 458)
    - Wuhu General Hospital, Wuhu, 1934 - 1945 (Box 35, Folder 459)
    - Haichow area, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 463)
    - Haichow area and Kuling, 1904 - 1905 (Box 35, Folder 464)
    - Haichow and Wuhu, 1906 - 1939 (Box 36, Folder 465)
  - Topics
    - ASH Internment camp, 1943 - 1946 (Box 36, Folder 466)
    - German airplane that landed in Haichow, 1914 Nov (Box 36, Folder 467)
    - China visit of Carrel Morgan, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 468)
    - Lianyungang Special Stamp Booklet, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 469)
  - Scrapbooks / albums
    - Places, events, Kuling summer resort, 1907 - 1926 (Box 36, Folder 470)
    - Family, friends, scenes, 1910 - 1946 (Box 36, Folder 471-472)
    - Haichow period, mission families, etc., 1904 - 1920 (Box 36, Folder 473)
    - Haichow period, summer resort, etc., 1920s (Box 37, Folder 474)
    - Haichow period, Ellen Lavine Graham Hospital work, 1910 - 1930 (Box 37, Folder 475)
    - Haichow period, scenes, famine relief work, early 1900s (Box 37, Folder 476)
    - Carrel Morgan family visit to China, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 477)